A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Commission on Women's Health, SG 2, Series 4 FA462
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Commission on Women's Health, SG 2, Series 4
1993-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA462
14.15 Cubic Feet 35 letter document boxes, 2 half-letter document boxes, 1 legal document box.
Arrangement
The Commission on Women's Health files are arranged in 9 subseries.
Subseries 1: Correspondence. Subseries 2: Financial. Subseries 3: Grants. Subseries 4: Meetings. Subseries 5: Personnel. Subseries 6: Publications. Subseries 7: Travel. Subseries 8: Vendors. Subseries 9: Special Formats.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: correspondence, grants, meeting minutes, publications, and personnel files.
New York (N.Y.); Mental health; United States; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Public welfare; Public health; New York (State); Medical education; Medicine, Rural; Medical research; War relief
- Correspondence, 1
  - Correspondence, 1993 June-Sept. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993 Sept.-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1993 Nov.-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Jan.-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Feb.-March (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1994 March 7-11 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1994 March-April (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1994 April-May (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1994 May-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1994 June-July (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1994 July-Aug. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Aug.-Sept. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Sept.-Oct. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Oct.-Nov. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Nov.-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Jan.-Feb. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Feb.-March (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1995 March-April (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1995 April-May (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1995 May-June (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1995 June 1-9 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1995 June-July (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1995 July-Aug. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Aug. 1-17 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Aug. 21-23 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Aug.-Sept. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Sept. 5-18 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Sept.-Oct. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Oct.-Nov. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Nov.-Dec. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Jan. 3-22 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Jan.-Feb. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Feb.-March (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1996 March-April (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1996 April-May (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1996 May-June (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1996 June 3-28 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1996 July-Aug. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Aug. 6-16 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Aug.-Sept. (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Sept 5-9 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Sept. 10-16 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Sept.-Oct. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Oct.-Nov. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Nov.-Dec. (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Dec. 3-26 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Jan.-Feb. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Feb. 5-24 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Feb.-March (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1997 March 17-27 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, 1997 March-April (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1997 April-May (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1997 May-July (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1997 July-Aug. (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Aug. 6-20 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Aug.-Sept. (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Sept. 5-23 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Sept.-Oct. (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Oct.-Nov. (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Nov.-Dec. (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Dec. 11-23 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Jan. 5-22 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Jan.-Feb. (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence, 1998 Feb.-March (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence, 1998 March-Dec. (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Financial, 2
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted from scholarly access - financial material.
  - Briefing Book - Year 1, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Briefing Book - Year 2, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Briefing Book - Year 3, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Briefing Book - Year 4, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Working Papers - Year 2, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Working Papers - Year 3, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Working Papers - Year 4, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Statements, 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Grants, 3
  - Budget - Year 1, 1993 Oct. 15 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Budget - Year 1, 1993 Dec. 3 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Budget - Year 1, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - 94-45 Interim Report, 1993 Dec. 15 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - 94-45 Final Report, 1994 May 13 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - 94-45 FAS - Reconciliation - Year One, 1994 March 31 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - 94-45 FAS - Reconciliation, 1994 April 30 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - 94-45 Revisions, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - 94-45 Sponsored Project Budget Authorization, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - 94-45 Year One - Extended - Budget, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - 94-45 Interim Report - Extended, and Grant 94-84, 1994 Oct. 5 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - 94-45 Final Report - Extended, and Grant 94-84, 1995 May 1 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - 94-84 Sponsored Project Budget Authorization - Year Two - Accounts, 1994 June 29 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - 94-84 Narrative Report, 1999 June 8 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - 94-84, 95413 Extensions - Two, 1995, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - 95413 Sonsored Project Budget Authorization, 1995 Sept. 11 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - 95413 Narrative Report, 1999 June 8 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - 95447 Sponsored Project Budget Authorization, 1995 Aug. 7 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - 95447 Narrative Report, 1999 June 8 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - 96953 Sponsored Project Budget Authorization, 1996 Oct. 18 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - 96953 Sponsored Project Budget Authorization, 1997 Sept. 12 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - 980509, 998552, Contracts, 1998 April 15 (Box 17, Folder 96)
- Meetings, 4
  - Arrangements, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  - Attendance, 1994 Feb.-March (Box 18, Folder 98)
  - Attendance, 1994 April (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Attendance, 1994 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Attendance, 1995 April (Box 18, Folder 101)
  - Attendance, 1995 Sept. (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Attendance, 1996 April (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Briefing Book, 1994 Sept. 28-29 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Briefing Book, 1995 April 5-6 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Briefing Book, 1995 Sept. 20-21 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Briefing Book, 1996 April 10-11 (Box 18, Folder 107)
  - Briefing Book, 1996 Oct. 2 (Box 18, Folder 108)
  - Briefing Book, 1996 Oct. 2-3 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Briefing Book, 1997 April 15 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Briefing Book, 1997 April 15-16 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Briefing Book, 1997 Sept. 24-25 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Briefing Book, 1998 Jan. 27-28 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Briefing Book, 1998 Jan. 27-28 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Originals - Meeting 2, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Related - Agenda, Presenters and Purpose, 1998 Jan. 28 (Box 19, Folder 116)
  - Calendars, 1993 Aug. 1 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Center for Women's Health - Columbia Presbyterian - Eastside, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Commission on Women's Health Meeting, 1993 Sept. 22-23 (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Materials Concerning Commission on Women's Health Meeting, 1993 Sept. 22-23 (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Cosmos Club - House Guest, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Dinner, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - Dinner, 1994 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Dinner, 1995 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 124)
  - Dinner, 1996 April (Box 20, Folder 125)
  - Dinner, 1996 Oct. (Box 20, Folder 126)
  - Dinner, 1997 April (Box 20, Folder 127)
  - Dinner, 1997 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 128)
  - Dinner, 1998 Jan. (Box 20, Folder 129)
  - General, 1995 April (Box 20, Folder 130)
  - General, 1997 April (Box 20, Folder 131)
  - General, 1997 Sept. (Box 20, Folder 132)
  - Grant Planning - Ideas, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 133)
  - Hotel, 1994 Jan.-April (Box 21, Folder 134)
  - Hotel, 1994 Sept. 1994 (Box 21, Folder 135)
  - Hotel, 1995 April (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - Hotel, 1995 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 137)
  - Hotel, 1996 April (Box 21, Folder 138)
  - Hotel, 1996 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 139)
  - Hotel, 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 140)
  - Hotel, 1997 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 141)
  - Management, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 142)
  - Management, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 143)
  - Management, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 144)
  - Planning Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 145)
  - Planning Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 146)
  - Meal, 1995 April 5 (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Notes, 1994 March (Box 21, Folder 148)
  - Notes, 1994 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Notes, 1995 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Notes, 1996 April (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - Notes, 1996 Oct. (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - Notes, 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - Notes, 1997 Sept. (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Notes, 1998 January (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Notes, 1998 April (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - Staff, 1993 Nov. 15 (Box 21, Folder 158)
- Personnel, 5; Document Boxes 23-24.
  Select files are resticted from scholarly research, as noted.
  - Symposium - Honorarium, 1993-1994, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 170)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Brier, Pamela, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 171)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Burke, Sheila, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 172)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Dunlop, Joan, 1994-1998 (Box 23, Folder 173)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Futter, Ellen V., 1994-1998 (Box 23, Folder 174)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Gradison, Bill, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 175)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Hearn, Rudy P., 1993 (Box 23, Folder 176)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Heimbold, Charles A., 1993, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Ignagni, Karen, 1993-1996, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - McAfee, Robert E., 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 179)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - McNeil, Barbara, 1993-1999 (Box 23, Folder 180)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Mundinger, Mary, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 181)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Rodgers, Kathryn, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 182)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Rowland, Diane, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 183)
  - Symposium - Honorarium - Russel, Cristine, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 184)
- Publications, 6
  - Adolescent Girls Focus Group Report, 1997 March (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - Adolescent Girls Meeting Expenses, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - Adolescent Girls Survey Report - Mailing, 1997 October 8 (Box 25, Folder 191)
  - Adolescent Girls Survey Report - Printing, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 192)
  - Background Covers - Printing, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - Bass Howes Report, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 194)
  - Brown & Wyn - Charts and Special Report, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - Brown & Wyn - Fact Sheets - Reprints, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 196)
  - Brown & Wyn - Special Report - Wommen's Health - Related Behaviors and Use of Clinical Preventive Services, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 197)
  - Canada Papers - Printing, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 198)
  - Case Studies of Women's Health Centers: Innovations and Issues in Women-Centered Care - Report - Weisman, Carol S., 1997 Jan. (Box 25, Folder 199)
  - Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse (CASA) - College Drinking, 1994 June (Box 25, Folder 200)
  - Chart Book, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 201)
  - College/Bernard, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 202)
  - College Health Project, 1993-1997 (Box 25, Folder 203)
  - College Health Service - Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - Commision on Women's Health - Printing, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - Disease Fact Sheet - Cancelled, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - Domestic Violence - Fact Sheet, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 207)
  - Domestic Violence - Harderman, J. - Rewrite, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - Domestic Violence - Meetings, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 209-211)
  - Domestic Violence - Meetings - Participants and Presenters (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - Domestic Violence - Policy Report, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - Domestic Violence - Policy Report - Addressing Domestic Violence and Its Consequences, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - Domestic Violence - Policy Report - Violence Against Women, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 215)
  - Domestic Violence - Meetings - Registration List of Attending Observers, Presenters, Participants and Staff, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 216)
  - Domestic Violence - Rosenberg, M. - Transcript, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 217)
  - Domestic Violence - Symposium, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 218-219, Box 27, Folder 220)
  - Domestic Violence - Symposium - Mitchell, Maria K., 1995 (Box 27, Folder 221)
  - Domestic Violence - Symposium - Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 222)
  - Domestic Violence and Communications, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 223)
  - Domestic Violence and Mental Health Symposium - Printing, 1995, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 224)
  - Envelopes - Printing, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - Faculty Round Table, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Girl's Health - Adolescent Focus Group Report - Printing, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 227)
  - Girl's Health - 5th & 6th Graders - River East Elementary School - Transcript, 1995 Nov. 10 (Box 27, Folder 228)
  - Harvard Conference - Higher Education and the Health of Youth, 1995 April 6-7 (Box 27, Folder 229)
  - Health Care Reform - Comments, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - Health Care Reform - Hang Tag - Printing, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 231)
  - Health Care Reform - What is at Stake for Women? - Distribution (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Health Care Reform - What is at Stake for Women? - Policy Report, 1994 July (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Health Care Reform - What is at Stake for Women? - Printing, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Health Care Reform - What is at Stake for Women? - Transparencies, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Health Insurance and Access to Care: Issues for Women - Background Paper, 1994-1995 Jan. (Box 27, Folder 236)
  - Health Insurance and Access to Care: Issues for Women - Printing, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 237)
  - Helen Hayes Hospital - Conference, 1996 April 19 (Box 28, Folder 238)
  - Just Being Vi - A Personal Story About Violence in America, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 239)
  - Just Being Vi - A Personal Story About Violence in America, 1991-1994; 2014:FA462:040; 74 Photographic Slides (Box 28, Folder 239A)
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, cideo, digital media, library material, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique seperation number, as noted. Request to access open speacial formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - Loose Leaf Binders - Printing, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 240)
  - MDS Publicity & Agreement, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 241)
  - Mammography - Technical Report, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 242)
  - Managed Care: What's at Stake for Women? Leiman, Joan M., Presentation - Pace University School Law, 1995 Nov, 17 (Box 28, Folder 243)
  - Melanie Gold, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 244)
  - Menopause and Depression, 1978, 1993, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 245)
  - Mental Health Background - Comments, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 246)
  - Mental Health - Background Papers - Distribution, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 247)
  - Permission to Reprint, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 248)
  - Prevention & Women's Health: A Shared Responsibility - Comment, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 249)
  - Prevention & Women's Health: A Shared Responsibility - Policy Report, 1996 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - Prevention & Women's Health: A Shared Responsibility - Printing, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 251)
  - Prevention & Women's Health: A Shared Responsibility - Reprint, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 252)
  - Prevention Policy Report - Envelopes - Printing, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Program on Women's Health - Pamplets, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Selected Facts on U.S. Women's Health - Chart Book, 1997 March (Box 29, Folder 255)
  - Survey of Women's Health, 1993 July 14 (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - Survey of Women's Health - Data, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 257)
  - Survey of Women's Health - Selected Press Clippings, 1993 Aug. 27 (Box 29, Folder 258)
  - The Health of College Women: A Rationale for Preventive Health Interventions - Cynthia A. Piltch - Review, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - The Health of College Women: A Rationale for Preventive Health Interventions - Technical Report, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 260)
  - The Health of College Women: A Rationale for Preventive Health Interventions - Technical Report Covers - Printing, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 261)
  - The Health of Women in the United States - Gender Differences and Gender-Specific Conditions - Background Paper, 1997 Feb. (Box 29, Folder 262)
  - The New School, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 263)
  - Three Way Delivery, 1995-1998 (Box 29, Folder 264)
  - Violence Against Women - Backgound Covers - Printing, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 265)
  - Violence Against Women - Background Covers - Reprint, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 266)
  - Violence Against Women - Background Paper - Comments, 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 267)
  - Violence Against Women - Background Papers - Distribution - First Edition, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 268)
  - Violence Against Women - Background Paper Revision - Substance Abuse - Fullilove, M., 1995 (Box 29, Folder 269)
  - Violence Against Women - Background Printing, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 270)
  - Violence Against Women - Background - Second Edition - Printing, 1996 April (Box 30, Folder 271)
  - Violence Against Women - Bunney, B. S. - Review, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 272)
  - Violence Against Women - Vello Bound - Printing, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 273)
  - Violence Against Women in the United States - Special Binding - Printing, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 274)
  - Violence Against Women in the United States - A Comprehensive Background Paper, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 275)
  - Violence Against Women in the United States - Understanding and Preventing Violence - Request to Reprint, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 276)
  - Walter, Heather - The Health of Adolescents, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 277)
  - Water, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 278)
  - Women and Health Care Reform, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 279)
  - Women and Mental Health - Glied & Kofman, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 280)
  - Women and Mental Health - Issues for Health Reform - Background Paper, 1995 March (Box 30, Folder 281)
  - Women and Mental Health - Issues for Health Reform - Distribution, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 282)
  - Women and Mental Health - Issues for Health Reform - Printing, 1995 March (Box 30, Folder 283)
  - Women and Mental Health - Issues for Health Reform - Reprint, 1995 Aug. (Box 30, Folder 284)
  - Women's Health - Related Behaviors and Use of Clinical Preventive Services, 1995 Oct.-Nov. (Box 30, Folder 285)
  - Women's Health Program Review, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 286)
  - Wordsmart, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 287)
  - Working Calendar of Products - Commission on Women's Health, 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 288)